Once upon a time,
从前，
there lived a naive
little plankton named Jack.
那里住着一个天真的人
名叫杰克的小浮游生物。
Jack's Chum Farm had
dried up,
杰克的密友农场有
干涸，
and he only had
one single farthing left
他只有
还剩一文钱
to buy food at the market.
去市场买食物。
Fear not, Karen,
my clockwork wife.
不要害怕，凯伦，
我的发条妻子
I will spend our
last farthing wisely
我将花费我们的
明智地最后一分钱
and save us from starvation.
使我们免于饥饿。
Mwah.
哇。
Oh!
哦！
Wah, wah, whee.
哇、哇、哇。
Get rich now?
现在发财了？
Magic bean?
魔豆？
Only one farthing?
只有一文钱？
Hmm.
唔。
Ka-ching!
嘉庆！
Ahh.
啊。
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
Ouch! Oh!
哎哟!哦！
Oh!
哦！
Oh, Karen.
哦，凯伦。
I hit the jackpot!
我中大奖了！
Thank King Neptune.
感谢海王星国王。
Did you get plenty
of food and varnish?
你得到很多吗
食物和清漆？
Better than that.
比那更好。
I got a magical bean.
我得到了一颗神奇的豆子。
What?
什么？
What do you do, boil it?
煮了怎么办？
You don't eat it.
你不吃它。
It's magic.
这很神奇。
Oh, Jack, I can't believe
you blew our last penny
哦，杰克，我不敢相信
你花光了我们最后一分钱
on a stupid bean.
在一颗愚蠢的豆子上。
I still need varnish,
我还需要清漆
but I'm not gonna let you
go hungry.
但我不会让你
挨饿吧。
Open wide.
敞开。
I told you, you don't eat it.
我告诉过你，你不吃它。
It's--
它是 -
Well, I'm full.
嗯，我吃饱了。
I told you so, Karen!
我告诉过你了，凯伦！
There he goes--
anything to win an argument.
他就在那里——
为了赢得争论而做的任何事情。
Whoa!
哇！
Hmm?
唔？
I don't care if they
are good for my heart.
我不在乎他们是否
对我的心脏有好处。
I am never eating another bean.
我再也不会吃其他豆子了。
Huh?
啊？
"Ye Old Krusty Krab"?
“老蟹堡”？
Maybe someone there
can make me rich.
也许有人在那里
可以让我变得富有。
Sounds like someone
is choking to death.
听起来像某人
快要窒息而死了。
Don't worry.
I'll save you!
不用担心。
我来救你！
Honk. Honk.
鸣喇叭。鸣喇叭。
Oh!
哦！
Galloping goose flesh!
奔腾的鹅肉！
I meant well, Karen!
我的本意是好的，凯伦！
Yeesh.
是啊。
Watch where you're pecking,
注意你啄的地方
you foul-feathered freak.
你这个羽毛肮脏的怪物。
What the--
什么是——
huh?
嗯？
Fee, fi, fo, fite.
费，fi，fo，fite。
I smell the blood
of a Bottomite.
我闻到了血的味道
一个Bottomite。
Oh?
哦？
Oh, it's just you, SpongeGoose.
噢，只有你，海绵鹅。
Whoo-hoo.
呼呼。
I have to stop feeding you
people food.
我必须停止喂你
人们的食物。
Be a good goose and lay
some Krabby Patties on me.
做一只好鹅并躺下
我身上有一些蟹肉饼。
Huh?
啊？
Magic harp, do your thing.
魔法竖琴，做你的事吧。
♪ Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow ♪
♪ 噢，噢，噢，噢，噢，
呜呜♪
Yeesh. Horrible.
是啊。可怕。
Whoa-oh-oh.
哇哦哦。
Ow!
噢！
Ow! Ow!
噢！噢！
Huh?
啊？
It's ready.
准备好了。
Edible gold, edible gold,
edible gold.
食用金，食用金，
可食用的黄金。
Huh? Ahh!
啊？啊！
Ooh.
哦。
Ahh.
啊。
I'm rich!
我很有钱！
Thank you, magic bean!
谢谢你，魔豆！
Oh?
哦？
Don't mind if I do.
如果我这样做的话，请不要介意。
Huh?
啊？
Who disturbs me inner sanctum?
谁扰我内殿？
Crazy weather, huh?
疯狂的天气吧？
Yipe!
哎呀！
Argh!
啊！
Got ya!
明白了！
Whether you're caged
or whether you're loose,
无论你被关在笼子里
或者无论你是否宽松，
I'll feed you
to me golden goose.
我喂你
对我来说是金鹅。
No, not the goose!
不，不是鹅！
No!
不！
I'll have a
solid gold pipsqueak...
我会有一个
纯金点滴...
in about four hours.
大约四个小时后。
Peekaboo!
躲猫猫！
What?
什么？
Giddy up,
galloping goose flesh.
头晕目眩，
奔腾的鹅肉。
Hya!
哈！
Bleh!
哎呀！
Huh? Whoa!
啊？哇！
Abandon goose!
放弃鹅！
I forgot geese can fly.
我忘记了鹅会飞。
All right, enough
of this storybook stuff.
好吧，够了
这本故事书的东西。
It's laser time, baby!
现在是激光时间，宝贝！
Timber!
木材！
Okay, you can keep the goose!
好吧，你可以留着鹅了！
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Karen!
凯伦！
Jack, look what you did
to our house.
杰克，看看你做了什么
到我们家。
I just slayed
a giant for you.
我刚刚杀了
对你来说是一个巨人。
You want to lay off?
你想裁员吗？
Oh.
哦。
Delicious.
可口的。
There you go.
就这样吧。
Bon appétit, sir.
祝你胃口好，先生。
You were right, darling.
你是对的，亲爱的。
That bean was magic.
那颗豆子很神奇。
Mwah.
哇。
Aww.
And what can I get
for you on this magical day,
而我能得到什么
在这个神奇的日子里为你，
my good sir?
我的好先生？
Ahh!
啊！
Um, I'd like a double
gold patty combo, please.
嗯，我想要双份
金色肉饼组合，请。
No shirt, no shoes,
没穿衬衫，没穿鞋子，
no shell, no service!
没有外壳，没有服务！
Take a hike, tiny.
去远足吧，小小。